I had something that like homeopathic
medicine wasn't gonna fix happen to me
recently my appendix was exploding I
mean I tried I was like lavender
lavender lavender
all my friends are like I should have
been frankincense
baby Jesus loves it
by the way your appendix explodes that's
weird like why do we have exploding
organs we don't even know why it blows
up it just picks a day just loses it the
appendix is just like nobody knows what
I'm for
[Music]
and you don't know that it's your
appendix that's exploding you don't have
a check appendix light on your body you
just have to figure it out go to WebMD
become a sleuth
look it up and I was like okay what's
going on with oh my gosh my ovaries I
did not know I had those
I've got a lot to work out this is
really a really bad day
I didn't think it was my ovaries I
thought it was what I ate that's
typically what people do they blame it
on what they ate and I had eaten a
burrito and I already have a plan for if
I eat a bad burrito I do a maneuver I
call it the poncho via push out
that's where you eat a second bigger
burrito push out the Madbury
[Applause]
works every time right it works
I know there's some dude in here who's
like I've done that it's not a poncho
via push-out
obviously if you're gonna do a bunch of
you push out don't be far from your home
be close to home don't be a hero to
burritos in your stomach play it safe
it's way too far from home it was a six
hour flight from home that's how far
from home I was as well I guess five
hours I was in New York City and I was
wandering around New York City two
burritos in my stomach
fighting seeing who's gonna be first at
stinko to my hole
that's gonna get a filter I'm sure ago
it's worth it
I had to fly home that night and my
flight was at 7 p.m. that got delayed
until 11 p.m. that's what life does to
you right when things are going bad life
will check in it'll be like hey how's it
going you'd be like not good life it's
that it's going really bad and life will
be like check it out what if I made it
worse no make it easier life life's like
I'm gonna make it worse it'll be funny
you'll see it's not on the plane till 11
didn't got off the plane until 2:00 a.m.
at 2:00 a.m. I was in so much pain I was
shuffling getting off the plane just
like oh I don't feel good
I had a burrito not a second one oh my
it was a bad idea I shouldn't have done
that
but everybody getting off a plane that's
been delayed it to em they all shuffle
they're like oh I don't feel good
the delayed flight Thank You JetBlue oh
and you see the other shuffle is you're
like oh did you have a failed push out
to follow me keep it clinched here we go
dude
and we're gonna gotta risk
I got home I tried to sleep I couldn't
sleep I was in too much pain that was
crazy I can't believe I couldn't sleep
because I was in too much pain
I googled something I'm embarrassed that
I googled this but I'm gonna say it I
googled how to fart that is what I
googled that's another filter that's
so many yoga poses came up you guys it
was just like just so many yoga poses if
you've ever been to a yoga class you'll
know that it happens and the instructor
always says the same thing they go and
if you have gas just let it be natural
they're like can I let it be hilarious
my body just turned into a bass kazoo
it's funny so put me on my floor at 3:00
a.m. just going get out get out down
there dog let's go get out I got bad
insurance you got to get out please
please get out and then I go go where is
your appendix and I went I should have
checked that one first
so I went to the hospital I gotta say I
did the right thing and if you're going
to the hospital I went out to the
interstate you know started checking
billboards to see who has the shortest
ER wait time
what on earth is that why is that an ad
campaign
sorry that doesn't mean you have a good
er it makes me imagine that there's like
this charge nurse somewhere that's like
how's room number one and they're like
we lost him and they're like great are
you billboards gonna be so low so we
wandered around for 15 minutes and saved
seven minutes and got right in they did
a scan of my body and they were like it
looks like you ate a little burrito and
then a bigger burrito why'd you do that
that was a dumb idea yeah you're not
very smart it's called the pone should
be a push-out I thought was a good idea
[Music]
they didn't say that they were like it's
your appendix your appendix is inflamed
and it's about to explode so we got to
do emergency surgery and I was like oh
thank heavens she was like thank heavens
and I go I thought it was something else
she goes what do you think it was and I
was like none of your business
I'm not here to talk about that so they
did my appendectomy they did it
laparoscopically has anybody ever had an
appendectomy and you go right up front
you guys there yeah did you have it done
laparoscopically yeah
same you know Lafayette you have a scar
on your right hand side oh that's cool
so this is the old way they used to do
at vendek Tamizh your appendix is over
here on the right hand side good for you
to know so you don't have to eat two
burritos
it used to cut you open where your
appendix is and take it out and that
makes sense to me based on my knowledge
of surgery from the game operation we
want to reach in don't touch the sides
and get it and and so when they do it
laparoscopically they cut you on the
other side and you find yourself going
guys it's so much closer if you just
went right here you just go right here
you're gonna punch a bunch of stuff and
my nose is gonna be like me
not good and they said don't worry we're
gonna inflate you some nothing will be
in the way and I was like that wasn't in
the game understand this so they did
that they inflated me through my
bellybutton a hole they made in my
bellybutton when they say they're gonna
inflate you through your bellybutton
it's impossible and not picture the
doctor at your bellybutton with a straw
just the circle to the surgical techs
like you got to pinch it otherwise they
are doesn't go in there we go
[Applause]
when they get it out goes well hunters
did they get it out in time you didn't
it didn't explode yeah was it close
no not even close whoo that's
interesting where's yours close your use
exploded oh I'm glad you're still here
what did they do when it explodes they
just go sorry another hole and they
drained you gross like a can of tuna
I mean it's cool that they didn't they
didn't give you a hard time they were
like they when they took it out were
they like we didn't even need to do that
it's fine
oh here's the bill ten thousand dollars
did you get billed you get billed if it
doesn't explode okay so it doesn't even
matter
welcome to the United States of America
doesn't even matter that's
you
hey did you know that Drybar comedy has
their own app now download it right now
and you can watch my whole special